vanillagift.com 2015-03-17

# 

                                                                                             Rev. 07/2013
                                 The Bancorp Consumer Privacy Notice
                                      What Does The Bancorp Do
FACTS:
                                 With Your Personal Information?
                     Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law
Why?                 gives consumers the right to limit some, but not all, sharing. Federal law also
                     requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information.
                     Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or
                     service you have with us. This information can include:
                           § Social Security Number and income
                           § Account balances and transaction history
                           § Credit history and credit scores
                     When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information, as
                     described in this notice.
How?                 All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their
                     everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies
                     can share their customers’ personal information, whether The Bancorp shares your
                     information, and whether you can limit this sharing.
        Reasons We Can Share                        Does The Bancorp                  Can you limit
      Your Personal Information                             share?                    this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes —
Such as to process your transactions,
maintain your account(s), respond to court                    Yes                             No
orders and legal investigations, or report to
credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes —
                                                              Yes                             No
To offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial
                                                               No                      We don’t share
companies
For our affiliates’ everyday business
purposes —
                                                               No                      We don’t share
Information about your transactions and
experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business
purposes —                                                     No                      We don’t share
Information about your creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                             No                      We don’t share
                     Visit us at www.VanillaGift.com.
 Questions?

What We Do
How does The Bancorp           To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and
protect my personal            use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These
information?                   measures include computer safeguards and secured files and
                               buildings.
                               We also limit access to information to those employees for whom
                               access is necessary.
How does The Bancorp           We collect your personal information when, for example, you:
collect my personal
                                    §  open an account or apply for a loan
information?
                                    §  pay your bills or make a wire transfer
                                    §  provide account information
                               We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                               bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
                                    §  sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                        information about your creditworthiness
                                    §  affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                    §  sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                               State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                               limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                     Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                               financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                    §  Our affiliates include financial companies such as The
                                        Bancorp Bank and Bancorp Card Services Inc.
Nonaffiliates                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                               financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                    §  The Bancorp does not share your information with
                                        nonaffiliates.
Joint marketing                A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                               together market financial products or services to you.
                                    §  The Bancorp does not jointly market.
	                                                                                            Page 2 of 2
